("Hallelujah" by Jeff Buckley)
♪ I heard there was a secret chord ♪
♪ That David played and
it pleased the Lord ♪
♪ But you don't really
care for music do you ♪
♪ Well it goes like this
the fourth the fifth ♪
♪ The minor fall and the major lift ♪
♪ The baffled king composing Hallelujah ♪
♪ Hallelujah ♪
♪ Well your faith was strong
but you needed proof ♪
♪ You saw her bathing on the roof ♪
♪ Her beauty and the
moonlight overthrew you ♪
♪ She tied you to her kitchen chair ♪
♪ She broke your throne
and she cut your hair ♪
♪ And from your lips she
drew the Hallelujah ♪
♪ Hallelujah ♪
♪ Baby I've been here before ♪
♪ I've seen this room and
I've walked this floor ♪
♪ You know I used to live
alone before I knew you ♪
♪ And I've seen your
flag on the marble arch ♪
♪ And Love is not a victory march ♪
♪ It's a cold and it's
a broken Hallelujah ♪
♪ Hallelujah ♪
♪ Well there was a time
when you let me know ♪
♪ What's really going on below ♪
♪ But now you never
show that to me do you ♪
♪ But remember when I moved in you ♪
♪ And the holy dove was moving too ♪
♪ And every breath we
drew was Hallelujah ♪
♪ Hallelujah ♪
♪ Maybe there's a God above ♪
♪ But all I've ever learned from love ♪
♪ Was how to shoot
somebody who outdrew you ♪
♪ And it's not a cry
that you hear at night ♪
♪ It's not somebody who's seen the light ♪
♪ It's a cold and it's
a broken Hallelujah ♪
♪ Hallelujah ♪